<Result><clientId>BcouncildelhiBDWS01</clientId><format>7</format><resultCode>00</resultCode><hits>1</hits><from>0</from><to>1</to><data><?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<data>
<record>
<ISBN13>9780521669948</ISBN13>
<ISBN13H>978-0-521-66994-8</ISBN13H>
<FTS>Exploring Grammar in Writing</FTS>
<TL>Exploring Grammar in Writing</TL>
<CR1>A01</CR1>
<CRT1>By (author)</CRT1>
<CCI1>N</CCI1>
<CNF1>Rebecca Hughes</CNF1>
<CR1>A01</CR1>
<CRT1>By (author)</CRT1>
<CCI1>N</CCI1>
<CNI1>Hughes, Rebecca</CNI1>
<CR1>A01</CR1>
<CRT1>By (author)</CRT1>
<CCI1>N</CCI1>
<CNS1>Rebecca Hughes</CNS1>
<CR1>A01</CR1>
<CRT1>By (author)</CRT1>
<CCI1>N</CCI1>
<CNSI1>Hughes, Rebecca</CNSI1>
<HMM>247</HMM>
<WMM>190</WMM>
<SMM>15</SMM>
<WG>390</WG>
<PFC>BC</PFC>
<PFCT>Paperback</PFCT>
<PFD1>B102</PFD1>
<PFDT1>Trade paperback (US)</PFDT1>
<PAGNUM>176</PAGNUM>
<ILL>black &amp; white illustrations, colour illustrations</ILL>
<IMPN>Cambridge University Press</IMPN>
<PUBN>Cambridge University Press</PUBN>
<COP>United Kingdom</COP>
<IMPID>53220</IMPID>
<PUBID>53220</PUBID>
<NAC1>L</NAC1>
<NAT1>ELT / TEFL</NAT1>
<BIC2SC1>CFK</BIC2SC1>
<BIC2ST1>Grammar, syntax &amp; morphology</BIC2ST1>
<DEWS1>DC22</DEWS1>
<DEWEY1>428</DEWEY1>
<PRODCC>S1.5</PRODCC>
<PRODCT>Linguistics</PRODCT>
<LOCSH1>English language--Written English</LOCSH1>
<NBDSD>This book contains varied practice activities and a wide range of formal and informal text-types for upper-intermediate to advanced students.</NBDSD>
<NBDLD>This book contains varied practice activities and a wide range of formal and informal text-types for upper-intermediate to advanced students.  Exploring Grammar in Writing develops students' understanding of how genre, context and purpose affect grammatical choices in writing. The book provides 20 units of clear explanations, lively grammar practice exercises and writing tasks. Each unit focuses on a different area of writing and its typical language features. Using real written examples from the Cambridge International Corpus, Exploring Grammar in Writing helps learners improve both their grammatical awareness and their writing skills. This edition, with answers, is ideal for self-study.</NBDLD>
<NBDBIOG>Rebecca Hughes is Chair of Applied Linguistics at the University of Nottingham. She is the co-author of Exploring Grammar in Context (with Ronald Carter and Michael McCarthy) and author of Exploring Grammar in Writing both with Cambridge University Press. Her other main research interests are in spoken language, and language policy for Higher Education.</NBDBIOG>
<NBDTOC>Contents  Acknowledgements    Introduction    Part 1 Writing for different readers  1 Everyday notes        Shortening the message by using ellipsis  Common abbreviations and when to use them  2 Greetings Cards        Conventional expressions used for different occasions  Varying the warmth and formality of the message  3 Formal letters and e-mails       Expressing requests for action and making suggestions  Combining modals and conditionals to make requests  4 Policies and agreements       Modals and semi-modals of obligation  Formal versus informal language choices  Part 2 Building noun phrases  5 Business letters        Patterns of noun phrases  Writing opening statements  6 Hobby books        Using articles with countable and uncountable nouns  Degree adverbs  7 Informal letters and e-mails       Using articles to show shared knowledge  Handling vague language.  8 Catalogues        Building noun phrases using for and with  Adjectives which take prepositions  9 Technical manuals        Nouns pre-modified by other nouns  Prepositions used to express precise actions  Part 3 Adding more information to the sentence  10 Encyclopaedias        Defining and non-defining relative clauses  Starting a relative clause with a preposition  11 Blurbs         Adding information at the start of a clause  Variations in noun pre-modification  12 Holiday brochures        Expanding the sentence using co-ordination  Handling adjective choices  13 Travel guides        Adding information to the noun by apposition  Varying the style by moving appositional phrases  14 Direct mail        Adding comparative and superlative structures to the sentence  Adjectives that do not normally take comparative or superlative forms  Part 4 Sequencing and focusing  15 Everyday instruction booklets       Non-finite clauses: -ing and to ...   Prepositions introducing -ing clauses  16 Newspaper stories        Handling and combining adverbs of time and place  Adverb phrases starting with prepositions  17 Packaging        Various styles of instructions  Reduced imperatives  18 Advertisements        Using adverbs for emphasis  Using only for focus  19 Essays         Comparing approaches  Making your own point and supporting it with references  20 Feature articles        Interesting the reader and changing the focus using it  Adjectives and verbs commonly used in it clauses  Key         Glossary         Index</NBDTOC>
<ERSL>WOW</ERSL>
<PUBPD>20050728</PUBPD>
<PUBSC>04</PUBSC>
<PUBST>Active</PUBST>
<AUSLPUBNAME>Cambridge University Press</AUSLPUBNAME>
<AUSLPUBD>20050728</AUSLPUBD>
<GBPCCPRRRP>18.40</GBPCCPRRRP>
<GBPCCPRRRPLT>18.40</GBPCCPRRRPLT>
<GBPCCPLCD>20140103</GBPCCPLCD>
<GBPCCPTC>02</GBPCCPTC>
<GBPCCPTD>RRP including tax</GBPCCPTD>
<USDCCPRRRP>28.25</USDCCPRRRP>
<USDCCPRRRPLT>28.25</USDCCPRRRPLT>
<USDCCPRPN>Local taxes may apply</USDCCPRPN>
<USDCCPTC>01</USDCCPTC>
<USDCCPTD>RRP excluding tax</USDCCPTD>
<AUDCCPRRRP>29.95</AUDCCPRRRP>
<AUDCCPRRRPLT>27.23</AUDCCPRRRPLT>
<AUDCCPLCD>20140116</AUDCCPLCD>
<AUDCCPTC>02</AUDCCPTC>
<AUDCCPTD>RRP including tax</AUDCCPTD>
<NZDCCPRRRP>37.95</NZDCCPRRRP>
<NZDCCPRRRPLT>33.00</NZDCCPRRRPLT>
<NZDCCPLCD>20140116</NZDCCPLCD>
<NZDCCPTC>02</NZDCCPTC>
<NZDCCPTD>RRP including tax</NZDCCPTD>
<EURCCPRRRP>18.36</EURCCPRRRP>
<EURCCPRRRPLT>18.36</EURCCPRRRPLT>
<EURCCPRPN>Local taxes may apply</EURCCPRPN>
<EURCCPLCD>20060311</EURCCPLCD>
<EURCCPTC>01</EURCCPTC>
<EURCCPTD>RRP excluding tax</EURCCPTD>
<UKNBDPASLCD>20110722</UKNBDPASLCD>
<UKNBDPAC>20</UKNBDPAC>
<UKNBDPAT>Available</UKNBDPAT>
<AUSNBDPASLCD>20110722</AUSNBDPASLCD>
<AUSNBDPAC>22</AUSNBDPAC>
<AUSNBDPAT>To order</AUSNBDPAT>
<NZNBDPASLCD>20110722</NZNBDPASLCD>
<NZNBDPAC>22</NZNBDPAC>
<NZNBDPAT>To order</NZNBDPAT>
<USNBDPAC>21</USNBDPAC>
<USNBDPAT>In stock</USNBDPAT>
<EURNBDPASLCD>20060311</EURNBDPASLCD>
<EURNBDPAC>97</EURNBDPAC>
<EURNBDPAT>No recent update received</EURNBDPAT>
<INNBDPASLCD>20130918</INNBDPASLCD>
<INNBDPAC>23</INNBDPAC>
<INNBDPAT>POD</INNBDPAT>
<UKADN1>Cambridge University Press</UKADN1>
<UKADI1>53220</UKADI1>
<AUSADN1>Cambridge University Press</AUSADN1>
<AUSADI1>109981</AUSADI1>
<USADN1>Cambridge University Press</USADN1>
<USADI1>9010000000000011453</USADI1>
<NZADN1>Cambridge University Press</NZADN1>
<NZADI1>109981</NZADI1>
<SAADN1>Cambridge University Press (South Africa)</SAADN1>
<SAADI1>120803</SAADI1>
<SAADN2>On the Dot</SAADN2>
<SAADI2>182082</SAADI2>
<IRLADN1>Cambridge University Press</IRLADN1>
<IRLADI1>53220</IRLADI1>
<INADI1>266208</INADI1>
<INADI2>62652</INADI2>
<INADN1>Cambridge University Press, India</INADN1>
<INADN2>Atlantic Publishers &amp; Distributors Pvt Ltd</INADN2>
<WSLRUK>GARD</WSLRUK>
<WSLREXUK>BTB ING</WSLREXUK>
<IMAGFLAG>Y</IMAGFLAG>
</record>
</data>
</data></Result> 
